(Zack:)So, long story short,
I nailed her.
(Sheldon:)When he finished,
he shouted "Eureka!"
No, I always shout, "Holy moly!"
(Sheldon:)Don't know why.
Just do.
(Sheldon:)All right, that concludes
the "getting to know you"
portion of the evening.
(Sheldon:)Who's ready to play some
vintage video games?
(Sheldon:)And tonight's selections include
ColecoVision's "Smurf Rescue
in Gargamel's Castle,"
Atari's "Cookie Monster Munch,"
(Sheldon:)and for you
text adventure aficionados,
"Zork."
(in high voice):
Pick me, pick me. I'm fun.
(Barry:)That all sucks
the big hairy meatball.
(Barry:)How about I go get
the karaoke machine
out of my car,
(Barry:)get plastered and blow
the roof off this place?
(Zack:)Great, I'll make a beer run.
(Stuart:)And I'll take a shower.
We'll meet back here in 15.
(Amy(on phone):)Check.
(door closes)